Finding Aid for the Robert Litz papers, 1979-2012
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Motion Picture Projects.
  - Bub., no date. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bub., c. 1993. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Case of Rape (A) - outline., 1995 Sept 12. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Cassatt., no date. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Cassatt and Degas., 1995, 2007-2008. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Christmas at Larks Hill., no date. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Citizen Khoury., 2009 Aug 2. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Citizen Khoury. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Cloak & Dagger., 1994 Aug 1. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Cold (The) - treatment., no date. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Crawling Eye (The) - treatment., no date. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Cut Outs (The)., 2009 Oct 12. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Date With Eternity., c. 1992. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Diary (The)., no date. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Discomfort Zone., ca. 2012. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Divine Right., no date. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Divine Right., 1989 July. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Divine Right., no date. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Divine Right., 1995 Apr 20. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Earthlings - treatment., no date. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - ecks., 1988 Nov 5. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - ecks., 1989 Aug 16. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Ex-., no date. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Family X-Mas (A)., 2007 July 15. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Fighting City Hall. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - First Run - treatment., 1987 Mar 15. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - For the Price of a Mule - treatment., no date. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Franklin., 1994 Sept 1. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Frontier Justice., no date. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Frontier Justice., 2008 June 1. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Game Cop., no date. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Give a Girl a Break., 1985 Sept 30. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Goo., 2002 Feb - Mar. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Goo - outline., 2002 Apr 23. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    With pages from Goo novel.
  - Grail (The)., 2008 May 3. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Honolulu., 2007-2008. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - House of Cards., 1985 Feb 27. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Imaginary Sins., 2006. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Imaginary Sins., 2006 Apr 10. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Inca., ca. 1998. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Isadorable - outline., 2005. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Jerusalem., 1987 Sept 25. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Juarez., 2005-2006. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Juarez., no date. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Julie Hiatt Steele., ca. 2001. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jumpers., no date. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Jumpers., no date. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Juniors., c. 1982. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Last Chance., no date. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Last Chance., no date. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Last Neanderthal (The)., no date. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Last Neanderthal (The)., no date. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Light (The)., c. 1983. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Like a Kick in the Head., no date. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Little People., 1985 June 7. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Long Beach., ca. 1996. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Madeleine's Ghost., 1997 June. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Magic Salad., c. 1982. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Massie - outline and notes., ca. 2007. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Medium Straight., no date. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Medium Straight - promotional materials., ca. 1988. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Medium Straight - promotional materials., ca. 1988. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Mobile Hymn., no date. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    Appears related to Mobile Hymn.
  - Mobile Hymn., 2000 July 22. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Mont-Royal., ca. 2006. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Mont-Royal., no date. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Mont-Royal - pitch., no date. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - National Treasure., 1996 Nov. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - National Treasure., no dates. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - National Treasure., ca. 1999. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Night Job., ca. 2005. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Nightmagic., no date. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Nightmagic., 1991 Jan. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Nightmagic., 2008 Dec. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Off the Deep End., no date. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - On the Sly., no date. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - On the Sly., no date. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - One Fell Swoop - treatment., no dates. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - One World., no date. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Other Half of the Mirror (The) - outline., no date. (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Peoples Park., no date. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Playing the Room., 2008-2009. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    With cd recording of interviews.
  - Playing the Room., ca. 2008. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Pounding Turf., 1996 Dec. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Pounding Turf., 1989 Aug. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Rachel Variant (The)., ca. 2005. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Rachel Variant (The)., 2012 May 30. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Raiders., 1986 Oct 1. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Raiders., 1986 Oct 1. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Raney., 1987 May 23. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Rappin'., ca. 1985. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Rappin'., 1985 Jan. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Reckless., c. 1982. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Screenwriter to the Mob., no date. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Screenwriter to the Mob., no date. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Showdown at Rainbow Creek - treatment., no date. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Sinbad: Beyond the Veil of Mists., 1997 Dec 2. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Stuck in Jersey., no date. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Stuck in Jersey., no date. (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Stuck in Jersey., no date. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Swashbuckle., no date. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Swashbuckle., no date. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Swashbuckle., 1997 Apr. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Swashbuckle., no date. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Ten Tricks., no date. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Ten Tricks., 2003-2005. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Ten Tricks - cast and crew list., no date. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Ten Tricks - production information (15 folders)., ca. 2004. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - T-Floor., 1985 May 26. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - T-Floor., 1984 Oct 27. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Treatments for various projects., no dates. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Twister - legal., 1984 Aug - Nov. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Unidentified script., no date. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Untitled Marie Torre Project - outline., no date. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Weatherman., no date. (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - West., no date. (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Television Projects.
  - Almost Perfect., 1994 Nov 13. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Alta California., 2004 Aug 1. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Episode One - 14 to Life.
  - Alta California., 2008 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alta California., 2004. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alta California., 2008 Jan. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alta California., 2004 Aug 1. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Episode Three - Beginnings.
  - Alta California., 2004 Feb. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alta California., 2004 Aug 1. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Episode Two - Poster Girl.
  - Alta California., ca. 2005. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alta California., 2004 Feb 11. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Episode Two - Self Incriminations.
  - Alta California - presentation script., no date. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Big Sky., no date. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Chinatown., 1999 Apr 23. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Chinatown., ca. 1998-1999. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Chinatown., 1999 July 10. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Chinatown - edit draft., 2000 Mar 16. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Chinatown - research and notes., ca. 1999. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Coop., ca. 1990s. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Crack Dragon., ca. 2006. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Crack Dragon - pitch., ca. 2006. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Fit to Print., 2009 Oct 23. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Pilot - Let the Games Begin.
  - Fit to Print., 2009 May 7. (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Fit to Print., no date. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Fit to Print - pitch., no date. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Hunting of the President (The)., 2001 June 20. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Hunting of the President (The)., 2001 May - June. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Hunting of the President (The)., ca. 2000. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Hunting of the President (The)., 2001 May - June. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Hunting of the President (The)., 2001 May 16. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Hunting of the President (The)., no date. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Hunting of the President (The)., 2001 May. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Hunting of the President (The) - Gore ads and other research., 2000-2001. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Hunting of the President (The) - notes., 2001 May. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Hunting of the President (The) - shots., 2001 May. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Kate Shugak, P.I.., 2009 Nov 10. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    Episode 1 - A Cold Day for Murder.
  - Kate Shugak, P.I.., 2009 Nov. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Laura & Charles., 1996 Aug - Sept. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Little Montana., no date. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Long Beach., no date. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Mario Andretti., no date. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    With notes and interviews.
  - NGO., no date. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Ransom of Red Chief (The)., no date. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Snow Runner., no date. (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Stevie Stardust., 1998 Sept 16. (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Sweet & Lorraine., no date. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    Pilot - Tissue of Lies.
  - Sweet & Lorraine - pitch., no date. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Sweet and Lorraine., no date. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Sweet Lorraine., ca. 2006. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Trojan Horse - treatment., no date. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Warrior Tradition (The)., 1995 Dec 18. (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - We've Come to Help., 1986, 1992. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - We've Come to Help., no date. (Box 33, Folder 10)
    Welcome to the War - pilot.
  - We've Come to Help., no date. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - We've Come to Help., 1999 Feb 10. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - We've Come to Help., no date. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    Episode 2 - If Music Be the Food of Love.
  - We've Come to Help., no date. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - We've Come to Help., 1999 Oct 22. (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - We've Come to Help - pitch., no date. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Whistler's Mother - pitch., no date. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - WZOO., no date. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Yes, Miz Edith., no date. (Box 34, Folder 7)
- Book Projects.
  - Bub., c. 1994. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Bub., no date. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Every Move She Makes., no date. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    T.J. Maxwell mystery.
  - Perfect Rose (A)., no date. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Poisoned Ivy., c. 1990. (Box 23, Folder 6)
    T.J. Maxwell Mystery.
  - Poisoned Ivy., c. 1990. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Trust Fund Baby., no date. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Trust Fund Baby., no date. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Trust Fund Baby., no date. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Trust Fund Baby., c. 1994. (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Trust Fund Baby., no date. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Trust Fund Baby., no date. (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Essays.
  - Balanced Budget (The)., 1997 Feb 10. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - CGI Editing., 2008 Jan 28. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Essays., no date. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Essays on America., no date. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Hong Kong., ca. 1997 Feb. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - How President Bush Became a National Hero. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - In Defense of Sentiment., no date. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - In My Humble Opinion., 2000 Nov - Dec. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Ohio Essay., no date. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - On Privacy., no date. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - People's Temple (The): Fatal Stumble in the Jungle., ca. 2005. (Box 22, Folder 11)